purpleporno.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Purple Porno

PurplePorno SAS, a US corporate entity registered in the registry of commerce of the US, located United States of America, (hereinafter “PurplePorno”) processes Personal Data (as defined below) in the course of its business, including the Personal Data of people using and browsing the http://www.PurplePorno.com website (the “Site”).

The purpose of this “Privacy Policy is to inform all individuals to whom the Personal Data collected by 3DS relate (“You” or “Your”) how PurplePorno collects and uses such Personal Data and how You can control its use.

  1. **SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy sets forth the principles and guidelines governing the processing of Your Personal Data (as defined below) including the Personal Data collected on or through the Site.

Personal data (“Personal Data”) means any information that may result in the identification of an individual.

Non-Personal Data means any information that does not result in the identification of an individual.

For visitors and users of the Site, the Site’s Terms of Services, which can be found at _http://www.PurplePorno.com/terms-of-service_ are incorporated into this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site and any Personal Data You provide on the Site are subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and those Terms of Services.

  2. **DATA COLLECTED**

_For visitors and users of the Site_ : in order to use certain functions and features of the Site, 3DS requires that You provide certain Personal Data when visiting or using the Site. You are free to decide whether or not to provide all or part of Your Personal Data. However, if You choose not to provide all or part of Your Personal Data, the purposes as described in section 4 might not be achieved or not properly achieved, some areas and functions of the Site may not function properly and/or You may be refused access to certain pages on the Site. In particular, You will not be authorized to purchase products or services via the Site.

  3. **PROTECTION OF PERSONAL DATA CONCERNING CHILDREN**

PurplePorno products and services are not designed to be marketed to children under the age of 18 and PurplePorno does not knowingly collect or store Personal Data from children under the age of 18.

However, certain PurplePorno products and services may be appropriate for use by children, and in that case children must seek consent from their parents prior to creating a PurplePorno account. Teachers and school administrators may act in the place of parents and provide consent for the collection of Personal Data from children (schools should always ensure that they have received permission from parents to do so).

If parents become aware that their child has provided PurplePorno with Personal Data without their consent or without a teacher’s or school administrator’s consent, they can ask PurplePorno to remove such Personal Data and terminate the child’s account by sending an email to: security@PurplePorno.com.

If PurplePorno becomes aware that it has collected Personal Data from a child under 13, PurplePorno will take steps to seek the parent’s consent for that processing or to remove such Personal Data and terminate the child’s account.

  4. **METHODS AND PURPOSES OF COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA**

Note that You provide Your Personal Data on a voluntary basis.

PurplePorno collects Personal Data online and offline (e.g., via a business card voluntarily given to a PurplePorno employee) and this Privacy Policy is applicable regardless of the means of collection.

Personal Data is generally collected to carry out the business of PurplePorno, such as improving PurplePorno’s marketing and advertising efforts and better tailoring PurplePorno products and services to customers’ needs.

Your Personal Data collected by PurplePorno on or through the Site may be used by PurplePorno for the following purposes:

  * To enable You to request information;
  * To provide You with a personalized interactive use of the Site;
  * To ascertain Your requirements and interests and provide You with the most suitable products and/or services;
  * To allow You to open and maintain an account in order to obtain specialized documentation and technical assistance;
  * To enable You to subscribe to a commercial or a support service;
  * To enable You to make online purchases of some of our products;
  * To enable You to register for a seminar, webinar, or event;
  * To access all the features and options offered by the Site; and
  * Any other purposes associated with the above purposes..

By providing Your e-mail address, You hereby expressly authorize, PurplePorno and its affiliates to use it together with other relevant Personal Data to send You commercial or marketing communications.

PurplePorno might also use Your email address for administrative or other non-marketing purposes.

  5. **COOKIES**

Cookies are text files stored and used to record non-personal and personal information concerning Your browsing of the Site.

PurplePorno may use cookies or other technologies which may collect or store Personal Data to improve services for You through, for example:

  * enabling a service to recognize your device so You don’t have to give the same information several times,
  * recognizing that You may already have given a username and password so you don’t need to do so repeatedly,
  * measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there’s enough capacity to ensure they are fast,
  * analyzing data to help PurplePorno understand how people interact with the Site so PurplePorno can improve the Site.

PurplePorno may also use third party vendors to measure and analyze the effectiveness of the Site. In such a case, web beacons and cookies provided by such third party vendors may be used and stored.

PurplePorno may use two types of cookies: permanent cookies and temporary cookies. Temporary cookies disappear as soon as You log off from the Site. Permanent cookies remain after logging off from the Site in order to be used on subsequent visits to the Site.

You will be notified the first time You receive a cookie, and then You decide whether to accept it or refuse it. By continuing to use the Site in consideration of the above, You expressly authorize PurplePorno to use such cookies.

You can also configure Your browser software to refuse all cookies; if You do so, however, some areas and features of the Site may not function properly and/or You may not access some parts or services of the Site.

  6. **PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING AND STORAGE TERM**

Processing of Personal Data includes using, storing, recording, transferring, adapting, summarizing, amending, reporting, sharing and destroying Personal Data as necessary under the circumstances or as otherwise required by law.

All Personal Data that will have been collected will be stored for a limited duration that is relevant to the purpose of such collection and for so long as required by applicable law.

  7. **LINKS TO WEBSITES NOT CONTROLLED BY PURPLEPORNO**

This Site might offer links to third party Websites which may be of interest to You.

Unless PurplePorno receives Your express authorization, PurplePorno does not share any Personal Data with these third parties. However, PurplePorno may provide them with Non-Personal Data.

PurplePorno does not exercise any control over the content of third party Websites or the practices of these third parties in connection with the protection of Personal Data that they might collect and are thus not under the control of PurplePorno. Consequently, PurplePorno declines all liability for the content of third party websites or the practices of these third parties concerning the protection of Personal Data.

It is therefore Your responsibility to inform yourself as to these third parties’ privacy policies.

  8. **TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA**

If You are accessing the Site from a location outside of the European Union, please note that through Your continued use of the Site, which is governed by US law, the corresponding Terms of Services and this Privacy Policy, You are transferring Your Personal Data to the European Union and You consent to that transfer.

As a member of a global group, PurplePorno is able to use available technology to efficiently manage Personal Data and obtain such Personal Data online or otherwise throughout its affiliates’ international operations.  Personal Data may be collected through the Site and subsequently disclosed to and used by an affiliate of PurplePorno (along with PurplePorno, “3DS Group Companies”) for the purposes stated in section 4 of this Privacy Policy.

Please note that PurplePorno may transfer Your Personal Data outside of the European Union, as long as before transferring Your Personal Data, PurplePorno has ascertained that non European Union entities, including PurplePorno’ affiliates and subsidiaries, offer an adequate level of protection in accordance with European legislation.  
Where PurplePorno has knowledge that a third party to which PurplePorno has provided Personal Data for the purposes listed in section 4 above, is using or disclosing Personal Data contrary to this Privacy Policy or to applicable laws, PurplePorno will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such use or disclosure.

You will have the opportunity to decide whether You authorize PurplePorno to use Your Personal Data for a purpose differing from the purpose for which it was originally collected.  
PurplePorno will also disclose Personal Data to third parties if PurplePorno determines that such disclosure is necessary for technical reasons (such as hosting services by a third party) or to protect PurplePorno’ legal interests (such as in the event of sale of assets to a third company, or change of control or total or partial liquidation of PurplePorno). Additionally, PurplePorno may share Your personal Data with the reseller assigned to You or in the territory where You are located. PurplePorno may also share Your personal data with business partners when PurplePorno and the business partner sponsor an event together or participate in a marketing promotion together and in which You engage.

PurplePorno may also disclose Your Personal Data if required by law or if PurplePorno believes in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (for example, a warrant, a subpoena, or other court order) or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of PurplePorno, our customers, or the public.

These transfers may be transmitted over the Internet, via mail, via facsimile, or by any other method that PurplePorno determines is appropriate and in accordance with applicable law.

  9. **RIGHT OF ACCESS TO AND RECTIFICATION OF THE DATA**

PurplePorno will take reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Data collected is used for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy and that such Personal Data is correct and up to date.

You have a right to access Your Personal Data. In addition, You have a right to request the rectification, completion, update and erasure of Your Personal Data. You also have a right to obtain a copy of the Personal Data stored by PurplePorno.

If You have an account, You may be able to exercise Your rights of access to and rectification of the Personal Data by logging on to Your account. Otherwise, You may exercise Your rights of access to and rectification of the data by writing at PURPLEPORNO, Legal, 10 place de la Madeleine, 75008 US (France) or sending an email to the following address: security@PurplePorno.com.

Depending on the scope of the request, PurplePorno reserves the right to charge a reasonable fee to cover any out-of-pocket costs incurred in connection with such access, modification and deletion of Personal Data.  PurplePorno may deny access to Personal Data in limited circumstances, defined by applicable laws and regulations.

  10. **DATA SECURITY AND RECIPIENTS**

PurplePorno undertakes to ensure the protection and security of Personal Data that You choose to communicate, in order to ensure the confidentiality of Your Personal Data and prevent Your Personal Data from being distorted, damaged, destroyed or disclosed to unauthorized parties.

PurplePorno maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect Personal Data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, modification and destruction.  As part of those safeguards, PurplePorno employs sophisticated technology designed to protect Personal Data during its transmission and prevent transmission errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.  However, while PurplePorno strives to protect Your Personal Data, in light of the inevitable risks of data transmission over the internet, PurplePorno cannot guarantee full protection against any error occurring during the course of Personal Data transmission that is beyond PurplePorno’ reasonable control.

Since Personal Data may be confidential, access is limited to employees, contractors and resellers of 3DS Group Companies who have a need to know such data in carrying out their tasks. All the people who have access to Your Personal Data are bound by a duty of confidentiality and subject to disciplinary actions and/or other sanctions if they fail to meet these obligations.

However, it is important for You to exercise caution to prevent unauthorized access to Your Personal Data. You are responsible for the confidentiality of Your password and information appearing on Your account. Consequently, You must ensure that You log out of Your session in the event of shared use of a computer.

  11. **DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

Although PurplePorno has put in place reasonable safeguards to protect Personal Data, we recognize that there is no method of transmitting or storing Personal Data that is completely secure.  
However, PurplePorno is committed to ensure the privacy of Personal Data: if You have a reason to believe that the security of Your Personal Data has been compromised or misused, You should contact PurplePorno via the following address: security@PurplePorno.com.  
PurplePorno will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints regarding use and disclosure of Personal Data in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy. .  
Unauthorized access to Personal Data or the improper use of Personal Data may constitute offenses under local law and under the regulations in force within each company in the PurplePorno group.

  12. **CONTACT**

For any additional question concerning this Privacy Policy, or any request for rectification, completion, update, or deletion of Your Personal Data You may write at PURPLEPORNO, Legal, 10 place de la Madeleine, 75008 US (France) or send an email to the following address: security@PurplePorno.com

  13. **DATE OF ENTRY INTO FORCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND CHANGES TO IT**

This Privacy Policy may be updated at any time without further notice, according to PurplePorno’ requirements and circumstances, or when required by applicable laws and regulations.

Last modification: _This Privacy Policy was modified in June 2016._
